SFU Archives reference and display materials collection
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Sports Photographs, 1950 - 1980; F-247-2; 50 cm of textual records 972 photographs 73 contact sheets 81 negatives 26 slides
  - Soccer, 1965 - 1980; F-247-2-3; 6 cm of textual records 111 photographs 11 contact sheets 1 negative
    - Soccer Photographs (portraits, action), 1975 - 1979; F-247-2-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 247-14)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-3-3.
    - Soccer Photographs (game photos), [ca 1965] - [ca 1980]; F-247-2-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 247-14)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-3-4.
    - Soccer Photographs (game photos), [ca 1965] - [ca 1980]; F-247-2-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 247-14)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-3-5. Creator's original file classification code: Gabor Halasz, Bill Cunningham, Ed Moran.
    - Soccer Photographs (group and award photos), [ca 1965] - [ca 1980]; F-247-2-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 247-14)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-3-6. Creator's original file classification code: Kent Kallberg, Gabor Halasz.
    - Soccer Photographs (game photos), 1979 - 1980; F-247-2-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 247-14)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-3-7. Creator's original file classification code: Marcel G. Con?.
  - Swimming, 1965 - 1980; F-247-2-4; 6 cm of textual records 170 photographs 3 contact sheets 7 negatives
    Series consists of photographic material relating to the SFU swimming program that includes athletic events, practices, and both individual and team photos.
    - Swimming Photographs (portraits, team, men, women), [ca 1974] - [ca 1978]; F-247-2-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 247-14)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-4-1. Creator's original file classification code: Bill Cunningham.
    - Swimming Photographs, [ca 1976] - [ca 1979]; F-247-2-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 247-14)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-4-2. Creator's original file classification code: Bill Cunningham.
    - Swimming Photographs (portraits), 1979 - 1980; F-247-2-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 247-14)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-4-3. Creator's original file classification code: Bill Cunningham; Peak Publications.
    - Swimming Photographs (group photos), [ca 1965] - [ca 1980]; F-247-2-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 247-14)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-4-4. Creator's original file classification code: Bill Cunningham; Peak Publications.
    - Swimming Photographs (awards and staff), [ca 1965] - [ca 1980]; F-247-2-4-0-5 (Archival box - standard 247-14)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-4-5. Creator's original file classification code: Lake Oswego Photographers; Bill Cunningham.
    - Swimming Photographs (portraits), [ca 1978]; F-247-2-4-0-6 (Archival box - standard 247-14)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-4-6. Creator's original file classification code: Bill Cunningham.
    - Swimming Photographs (miscellaneous), [ca 1965] - [ca 1980]; F-247-2-4-0-7 (Archival box - standard 247-14)
      Creator's original file classification code: Columbian (Peter Battistoni); M&PR.
  - Track and Field, 1975 - 1980; F-247-2-5; 3 cm of textual records 68 photographs 1 contact sheet
    Series consists of photographic material relating to the SFU track and field program that includes athletic events, practices, and both individual and team photos.
    - Track and Field Photographs (miscellaneous), 1975 - 1979; F-247-2-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 247-15)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-5-1. Creator's original file classification code: UNS; West Coast Graphics; Bill Cunningham.
    - Track and Field Women's Athletic Photographs (portraits), 1977; F-247-2-5-0-2 (Archival box - standard 247-15)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-5-2.
    - Track and Field Women's Athletics Photographs (portraits, team), 1978 - 1980; F-247-2-5-0-3 (Archival box - standard 247-15)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-5-3. Creator's original file classification code: Bill Cunningham.
  - Women's Athletics, 1965 - 1980; F-247-2-6; 5 cm of textual records 100 photographs 4 contact sheets
    Series consists of photographic material relating to the SFU women's athletics program that includes athletic events, practices, and both individual and team photos.
    - Women's Athletics Photographs - Track and Field, [ca 1965] - [ca 1980]; F-247-2-6-0-1 (Archival box - standard 247-15)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-6-1.
    - Women's Athletics Photographs - Portraits, [after 1972]; F-247-2-6-0-2 (Archival box - standard 247-15)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-6-2. Creator's original file classification code: Peak Publications Photo Services.
    - Women's Athletics Photographs - Volleyball (team, action shots), [ca 1975] - [ca 1980]; F-247-2-6-0-3 (Archival box - standard 247-15)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-6-3. Creator's original file classification code: Bill Cunningham.
    - Women's Athletics Photographs - Basketball, [ca 1975] - [ca 1980]; F-247-2-6-0-4 (Archival box - standard 247-15)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-6-4. Creator's original file classification code: Bill Cunningham.
    - Women's Athletics Photographs - Field Hockey, [ca 1975] - [ca 1980]; F-247-2-6-0-5 (Archival box - standard 247-15)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-6-5. Creator's original file classification code: Bill Cunningham.
  - Wrestling, 1950 - 1980; F-247-2-7; 12 cm of textual records 264 photographs 18 contact sheets 63 negatives 26 slides
    Series consists of photographic material relating to the SFU wrestling program that includes athletic events, practices, and both individual and team photos.
    - Wrestling Photographs, [ca 1968] - [ca 1975]; F-247-2-7-0-1 (Archival box - standard 247-16)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-7-1. Creator's original file classification code: Peak Publications Photo Services; SFU AVC; West Coast Graphics.
    - Wrestling Photographs (individual shots), [ca 1968] - [ca 1975]; F-247-2-7-0-2 (Archival box - standard 247-16)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-7-2.
    - Wrestling Photographs (portrait, group, event photos), [ca 1968] - [ca 1975]; F-247-2-7-0-3 (Archival box - standard 247-16)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-7-3. Creator's original file classification code: Bill Cunningham.
    - Wrestling Photographs (events), [ca 1979] - [ca 1980]; F-247-2-7-0-4 (Archival box - standard 247-16)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-7-4.
    - Wrestling Photographs (events, meets), [ca 1979] - [ca 1980]; F-247-2-7-0-5 (Archival box - standard 247-16)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-7-5.
    - Wrestling Photographs (individual shots, events, meets), [ca 1968] - [ca 1980]; F-247-2-7-0-6 (Archival box - standard 247-16)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-7-6. Creator's original file classification code: UNS.
    - Wrestling Photographs (events, meets, awards), [ca 1965] - [ca 1980]; F-247-2-7-0-7 (Archival box - standard 247-16)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-7-7.
    - Wrestling Negatives and Proofs, [ca 1965] - [ca 1980]; F-247-2-7-0-8 (Archival box - standard 247-16)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-7-8.
    - Wrestling Negatives, Proofs, and Photographs (events, meets), [195-] - [ca 1980]; F-247-2-7-0-9 (Archival box - standard 247-16)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-7-9.
    - Wrestling Slides, [ca 1965] - [ca 1980]; F-247-2-7-0-10 (Archival box - standard 247-16)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-7-10.
    - Photocopies of Wrestling Photographs (individual, events, meets, portraits), [ca 1965] - [ca 1980]; F-247-2-7-0-11 (Archival box - standard 247-16)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-7-11.
  - Miscellaneous Sports: Cricket, Fencing, Hockey, Rugby, 1965 - 1980; F-247-2-8; 5 cm of textual records 18 photographs
    Series consists of photographs materials documenting SFU participation in various sports that include cricket, fencing, hockey, rugby, and mountain climbling.
    - Miscellaneous Sport - Cricket, [ca 1965] - [ca 1980]; F-247-2-8-0-1 (Archival box - standard 247-15)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-8-1.
    - Miscellaneous Sport - Fencing, [ca 1965] - [ca 1980]; F-247-2-8-0-2 (Archival box - standard 247-15)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-8-2.
    - Miscellaneous Sport - Hockey, [ca 1965] - [ca 1980]; F-247-2-8-0-3 (Archival box - standard 247-15)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-8-3.
    - Miscellaneous Sport - Rugby, [ca 1965] - [ca 1980]; F-247-2-8-0-4 (Archival box - standard 247-15)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-8-4.
    - Miscellaneous Sport - Moutain Climbing, [ca 1965] - [ca 1980]; F-247-2-8-0-5 (Archival box - standard 247-15)
- People Files, 1900 - 1998; F-247-3; 86 cm of textual records 466 photographs 3 contact sheets 7 negatives 2 slides 2 videocassettes: VHS 1 cassette tape and other material
  Series consists of photos, negatives, contact sheets, slides, articles, press releases, poems, biographical notes, posters, audio and video tapes, and correspondence relating to individuals deemed significant by the Media and Public Relations Office. For a list of individuals associated with the sub-series, see file list.
  Roy Allan; Hortensia Allenda; Archie, Allison; Anderson, David; Liisa Atva; Don Baird; Bakan, Paul; Vivian Banci; Volodimir Barabash; Barlow, John S.; Mary Batchelor; Ronald H. Bayes; Owen Beattie; Lorna J. Bennett; Bentall, Charles; Jean Bergman; Rosalie Bertell; Birge, Bill; Hoffman; Hugo Blanco; Michael Bliss; Doreen Boal; Boubaker, Adjali; Jim Boyde; Boyle, Peter S.; Briemberg, Mordecai; Peter Brock; Buchanan, Charles A.; Mullen, Buell; Erich Burkle; Kenneth Burstein; Gaye Burton; Win Caldwell; Cameron, Brent; Campbell, Emily A.; Campbell, Gordon; Dawn Caniwell; Cao, Caroline; Deirdre Caprani; Patricia Carney; Wayne Carr; Carter, Bob; Gordon Chalmers; Chambers, D.O.; Eddy Chan; Po-Ying Chan; Poh-Yu Chan; Cheng, Pao; Joseph K. Cheung; Dennis Chow; Hans Christiansen; Peter Chrzanowski; Frazee, Dave; Rob Murray; Steiner, Beat; Jack Chutka; Glen Clark; Clarke, Margaret; Douglas Clement; Robert Coambs; Coates, Penny; Kevin Colbow; Mark Collins; Helen Cook; Cooper, Barbara; Cooper, David; Tina Cooper; Raymond Copes; Lynne Cove; John Crawford; Crawley, Jim; John Crispo; Lou Crockett; Crompton, Barbara; Maureen Crowley; Louise Cumming; Steward Cunningham; Dahl, Cecil; Dawson, Catherine; Graham Dawson; Dewick, Bernice; Ken Dietrich; Gordon Diewert; William Dimma; Herb Doman; Dunn, John; Marc Edge; Phillip Eidsvik; Emery, Brian; Ted Enoch; Miguel Estrella; Samia Fadl; Fellman, Anita; Felter, James W.; Marcia Findley; Fisher, Ann; Norah Flynn; Sandra Foulds; Fox, Terry; Fraser family; Fraser, Simon; Garr, Alan; Ghandi; Kate Gibbons; Mike Gidora; David Gillespie; Ted Glas; Gohier; John Grant; Dal Grauer; Greenhough, Karen; Guns, Brian; Haggerty, Sharon; Don Hahn; Hamilton, Charlotte Frances; Hara, Arthur; Harris, Joel; Joe Hoffman; Houlihan, Barry; Rick House; Howell, Ann Marie; Hunter, Trenna; Richard Hunwich; Mel Hurtig; Harold Adams Innis; Jewell, T. Ross; Grace Joe; Randi Johl; Terry Jones; Junta, Claude; Shyam J. Kamath; Shane Kaplin; Neil Kellock; Dr. Kelsey; Tom King; Young Hendy; George Kistiakowsky; Klassen, William; Peter Knowlden; Donald R.J. Knowles; Eddy Kronebusch; Shelah Kronebusch; Kersti Krug; Ronald Labonte; Lachs, Manfred; Lambert, Allen T.; LaPierre, Laurier; Leach, Joy B.; Dennis Lee; Walter Lever; Jim Livingstone; Pedersen, Knud George; Lord Fulton; Paul Lorimer; Tong Louie; Luke, Carmen; Clyve Lyttle; Mackintosh, Alec; Ted MacRae; MacWilliam, David; John Madden; McGeer, Pat; Galindo Madrid; Gary W. Magarrell; Keith Mah; Mainwaring, Brian; Phyllis Marling; Matsen; McBride, Anita; Stephen McCoach; Paul McFetridge; David McGeer; Ian McGregor; John McInnes; McIntosh, Patricia; McLaren, Juliet; Kevin McQuiggan; Melody, William H.; Millen, Bruce; Terry Miller; Karen Mittleman; Shannon Moeser; Gail Moser; Rob Muckle; Susan Musgrave; Elizabeth Neilson; Donald Nelson; Newman, Gerald M.; Ng, Kam Ling Evelyn; Nowlan, Alden; O'Donoghue, Anne; Malcolm Page; Madelene Parent; Derek Parkin; Patterson, Bruce; Kerry Pawlovich; Laurence Peter; Gordon Peterson; Norman Petroff; Janet Pinder; Popma, Anne; Mike Powley; Simon Priest; Keith Provan; Marke Raines; Harry Rankin; Jean Reed; Karen Rimmer; Kathleen Roberts; Roberts, Stanley; Robertson, Barb; Robertson, Bob; Sally Rowgow; John A. Ross; Ron Roy; Melody Rudd; Ryarson; Helen Salter; Robert Sass; Marg Sawyer; Diane Crowe; Rakesh Sayal; Roger Schiffer; John Seeley; Sens, Al; Moshe Shillow; Kari Siegler; Simson, Bernd; Rosalind Sinclair; Sinnott, Ted; Skulski, David; Zenon Smiechowski; Smith, Alan P.D.; Margaret Smith; Thomas J. Smith; Edith Speers; Keith Spicer; Stacey, Carolyn; Jan St. Amand; John Stark; Tracy Steadman; Gordon M. Summers; Gerry Swan; Gordon Edwin Swaters; Sharon Tarr; Gordon Thom; Thomas, Audrey; Jonathan Thornburg; Timberlake, Alan; John Toor; Florida Town; Trotter, Dave; Pierre Elliott Trudeau; Ed Tuner; Vanel, Kurtis; Mark Vulliamy; Randy Walker; Commander Waters; George Whalley; Williams, Ian; Wilson, John O.; Mel Woolley; Morris Wosk; Jake Wyman; Michael Yates
  All files are open unless indicated otherwise indicated. Files marked 'pending review' must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release, and as a result of the review, access restrictions may apply. Please see the file lists and consult the archivist for more details.
  - Allan, Roy; 3x4, [ca 1979]; F-247-3-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 247-17)
  - Allenda, Hortensia; 4x8, [ca 1980]; F-247-3-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 247-17)
  - Allison, Archie; 5x7, 1970; F-247-3-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 247-17)
  - Anderson, David; 5x7, 1972 - 1975; F-247-3-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 247-17)
    Creator's original file classification code: Ogloff, Pete.
  - Atva, Liisa; Co-op student (with Stephen McCoach); 5x7, 1984; F-247-3-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 247-17)
    Creator's original file classification code: SFU Week, July 19, 1984.
  - Baird, Donald A., University Archivist; 7+ 5x7; 1 8x10, Text, 1964 - 1982; F-247-3-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 247-17)
    Restricted in part
    Creator's original file classification code: Williams Bros.; M&PR.
  - Bakan, Paul; 7x9, [ca 1968]; F-247-3-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 247-17)
  - Banci, Vivian; Wolverine Research; 3 5x7; text, 1983; F-247-3-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 247-17)
  - Barabash, Volodimir; bio; "Poems from British Columbia" for D. Roberts, 1972; F-247-3-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 247-17)
    Creator's original file classification code: M D. Roberts.
  - Barlow, Dr. John S.; Biology, Associate Dean of Science; 4x6, 5x7; (1921-1991), F-247-3-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 247-17)
  - Batchelor, Mary, Departmental Assistant, Psychology (1943-1988), F-247-3-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 247-17)
  - Bayes, Ronald H.; 6 wallet (glossies), invitation, correspondence (copies), 1975; F-247-3-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 247-17)
  - Beattie, Owen; 8x10, 1973; F-247-3-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 247-17)
    Creator's original file classification code: John Denniston.
  - Bennett, Lorna J.; 5x7, [ca 1966]; F-247-3-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 247-17)
  - Bentall, Charles, [ca 1974]; F-247-3-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 247-17)
  - Bergman, Jean; 3x5, [ca 1975]; F-247-3-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 247-17)
  - Bertell, Rosalie; 5x5, [ca 1975]; F-247-3-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 247-17)
  - Birge & Hoffman; 3x3, [ca 1980]; F-247-3-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 247-17)
  - Blanco, Hugo; 3x3, [ca 1980]; F-247-3-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 247-17)
  - Bliss, Michael; 4x6, [ca 1975]; F-247-3-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 247-17)
  - Boal, Doreen, Admissions Office, 5x7; bio, 1983 - 1990; F-247-3-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 247-17)
  - Boubaker, Adjali; 3x5, [ca 1975]; F-247-3-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 247-17)
  - Boyde, Jim; 4x8, [ca 1980]; F-247-3-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 247-17)
  - Boyle, Peter; 5x7; bio, 1988 - 1990; F-247-3-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 247-17)
    Creator's original file classification code: Burnaby Now; M&PR.
  - Briemberg, Mordicai; 3 5x7, [ca 1970]; F-247-3-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 247-17)
  - Brock, Peter; 3x3, [ca 1975]; F-247-3-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 247-17)
  - Buell-Mullen; 2 8x10; 8x8 color, [ca 1965]; F-247-3-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 247-17)
    Creator's original file classification code: Columbian Newspaper.
  - Burkle, Erich; bio; 4 5x7, 1974; F-247-3-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 247-17)
    Creator's original file classification code: M&PR, UNS.
  - Burstein, Kenneth; 12 5x7; CV; bio; 1928-1987, 1969 - 1987; F-247-3-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 247-17)
    Creator's original file classification code: M&PR Comment 1978.
  - Burton, Gaye, 1984; F-247-3-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 247-17)
  - Caldwell, Win; 2 5x7, 1984; F-247-3-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 247-17)
  - Cameron, Brent; Grad Student, Education; New Teaching Methods the Way of the Future? July 21, 1986, F-247-3-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 247-17)
    Creator's original file classification code: M&PR news release.
  - Campbell, Emily; (with Tom Bennett) CD Nelson award winners; 2 5x7, 1984; F-247-3-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 247-17)
    Creator's original file classification code: SF Week Vol. 29, No. 9.
  - Campbell, Gordon; 1 5x7 (color), [ca 1988]; F-247-3-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 247-17)
    Creator's original file classification code: University Advancement?.
  - Caniwell, Dawn; SFU Rugby, 1985; F-247-3-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 247-17)
    Creator's original file classification code: SF Week, June 6, 1985.
  - Cao, Caroline (Giai Ly Cao); Shrum Entrance Scholarship winner, 1986; F-247-3-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 247-17)
    Creator's original file classification code: SF Week, Sept. 19, 1986.
  - Caprani, Deirdre; Claude E. Lewis Award, 1987; F-247-3-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
    Creator's original file classification code: Abbotsford News, June 10, 1987; M&PR news release.
  - Carney, Patricia; Psychological Association Gold Medal winner, 1985; F-247-3-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
  - Carr, Wayne; 2 5x7, 1984 - 1985; F-247-3-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
    Creator's original file classification code: SF Week Vol. 2, No. 9, etc..
  - Carter, Bob (oil-man with wife Sheilah establish scholarships), 1982; F-247-3-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
  - Chalmers, Gordon; 4 5x7; Governor General's Award, 1984; F-247-3-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
    Creator's original file classification code: M&PR: SF Week, June 7, 1984.
  - Chambers, D.O.; 5x7, [ca 1965]; F-247-3-0-0-43 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
  - Chan, Eddy; IMC (with member of Malaysia Pavilion Dance Troupe at Expo '86); 5x7, 1986; F-247-3-0-0-44 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
    Creator's original file classification code: M&PR: SF Week, Oct. 9, 1986.
  - Chan, Po-Ying, 1983; F-247-3-0-0-45 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
    Creator's original file classification code: M&PR: SF Week Vol. 26, No. 12 (July 28, 1983).
  - Chan, Poh-Yu; bio, [197-?]; F-247-3-0-0-46 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
  - Cheng, Pao; Business Administration; (pictured with Richard Shutler, Archaeology; Hamish Dickie-Clark, Sociology/Anthropology, 1987; F-247-3-0-0-47 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
    Creator's original file classification code: SF Week, Nov. 19, 1987.
  - Cheung, Joseph K.; bio and article, 1985 - 1989; F-247-3-0-0-48 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
  - Chow, Dennis, 1988; F-247-3-0-0-49 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
  - Christiansen, Hans, 1982; F-247-3-0-0-50 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
  - Chrzanowski, Peter; Frazee, Dave; Murray, Rob; Steiner, Beat, 1983 - 1984; F-247-3-0-0-51 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
    Creator's original file classification code: Alberta Report, M&PR, Province.
  - Chutka, Jack, Athletics, 1982; F-247-3-0-0-52 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
  - Clark, Glen; 2 5x7 (1 color), [ca 1998]; F-247-3-0-0-53 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
  - Clark, Meg; 5x7; Executive Director, Development, [ca 1997]; F-247-3-0-0-54 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
  - Clement, Douglas; 2 8x10; text, 1978; F-247-3-0-0-55 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
  - Coambs, Robert; 5x7, [ca 1975]; F-247-3-0-0-56 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
  - Coates, Penny, Director, SFU Daycare; 4 5x7; article, 1988; F-247-3-0-0-57 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
    Creator's original file classification code: SF Week, July 14, 1988.
  - Colbow, Kevin; Dr. E.J. Wells Chemistry Book Award, 1986; F-247-3-0-0-58 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
  - Collins, Mark; bio, article (Jan. 13, 1977), 1967 - 1977; F-247-3-0-0-59 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
  - Cook, Helen; Cashier's Office; 3 5x7, 1 8x10, 1979 - 1988; F-247-3-0-0-60 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
    Creator's original file classification code: Spotlight, Mar. 31, 1988.
  - Cooper, Barbara; SFU Graduate Student, 1988; F-247-3-0-0-61 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
    Creator's original file classification code: Coquitlam Sunday News.
  - Cooper, David; Rick Jones Memorial Award shared with Dan Sinclair; 5x7, 1981 - 1983; F-247-3-0-0-62 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
    Creator's original file classification code: New West Columbian, Mar. 23, 1983.
  - Cooper, Tina, 1998; F-247-3-0-0-63 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
    Creator's original file classification code: The Vancouver Sun.
  - Copes, Raymond; 2 degrees: BA and BSc.; son of Parzival Copes, 1983; F-247-3-0-0-64 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
    Creator's original file classification code: SF Week, June 9, 1983.
  - Cove, Lynne; Fitness Coordinator; 6 5x7, 1982 - 1984; F-247-3-0-0-65 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
    Creator's original file classification code: UNS: 84-11-08; SF Week, Sept. 12, 1982, Nov. 8, 1984.
  - Crawford, John W.; 5x7, [ca 1965]; F-247-3-0-0-66 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
    Creator's original file classification code: Peak?.
  - Crawley, Jim (Student Society President) & Parford, Pam; 8x10; text, 1981; F-247-3-0-0-67 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
  - Crispo, Dr. John; text, 1981; F-247-3-0-0-68 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
    Creator's original file classification code: M&PR SF Week.
  - Crockett, Lou; 5 5x7; 8x10; text, 1973 - 1984; F-247-3-0-0-69 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
    Creator's original file classification code: SF Week, Mar. 22, 1984.
  - Crompton, Barbara; founder of Fitness Group and Instructor, 1982; F-247-3-0-0-70 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
    Creator's original file classification code: Moose Jaw Times Herald.
  - Crowley, Maureen; 5x7; Player of the Week, [ca 1980]; F-247-3-0-0-71 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
  - Cumming, Louise; 5x7; text, 1981; F-247-3-0-0-72 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
  - Cunningham, Steward; 2 5x7; text, 1984; F-247-3-0-0-73 (Archival box - standard 247-18)
    Creator's original file classification code: UNS: 84-11-08.
  - Dahl, Cecil; 5x7, 1973; F-247-3-0-0-74 (Archival box - standard 247-18)